

I am a digital artist utilizing video, audio, photo, and code. From a young age I was always fascinated by computers; with the gift of a Visual Basic game programming book around age 8 I was plunged into a world of creating multimedia experiences. For me, the line between analytical and creative thinking is blurred- I prefer to operate in between the two.

#### **Education**

# **Bachelor of Arts in New Media, concentration in Motion Media Minor in Philosophy**

University of North Carolina at Asheville, Asheville NC

My education at UNC Asheville was filled with classes from many different departments ranging from new media, computer science, philosophy, and sociology, just to name a few. Having so many classes from different concentrations forced me to become well rounded and easily adaptable, while still primarily developing my skills as a digital artist.

## **Professional Experience**

Intern Web Developer UNCA's National Environmental Modeling and Analysis Center

Jan 2017 - Oct 2017

#### Dishwasher Chai Pani

Feb 2016 - Jan 2017

#### Technology Sales Associate Staples

Jan 2015 - Jan 2016

- Communicated with my mentor and members of the team in order to plan projects and suggest improvements.
- Designed a news board to allow scientists using FCAV-NEMAC's GIS Platform- to communicate more easily.
- Visualized and interpreted cohort data from FCAV in order to understand how often they visit, the order of pages viewed, how often they visit, and more.
- Worked with a large, fast-paced team in order to serve one of downtown Asheville's most popular destinations.
- Provided service and tech support to the customers visiting Staple's technology department.
- Stocked shelves following product display guides, took inventory, and used POS software to check customers out.

### **Volunteer Experience**

#### **Orange County Rape Crisis Center**

- Taught classes to high school boys on consent, sexism, and systemic oppression.
- Entered and interpreted data of thousands of responses from students before and after taking these classes.

## **Skills and Personal Prvojects**

- Maintaining my own VPS in order to host my portfolio and various web apps I've created.
- Research project utilizing NLTK in order to analyze the language used in Pitchfork in order to better understand how gender influences descriptive language.